<resources>

    <!-- LEARN ABOUT -->
    <string
        name="subject_learn_about">General Data Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Primary email address
        3 - Optional email address
    -->
    <string
        name="body_learn_about">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I would like to request your confirmation as to whether your organization is processing personal data concerning me, and, where that is the case, the following information:\n
\n
(i) the purposes of the processing;\n
(ii) the categories of personal data concerned;\n
(iii) the recipients or categories of recipient to whom my personal data have been or will be disclosed; if transferred to a third country or an international organization, what the appropriate safeguards for the transfer pursuant to Article 46 GDPR are;\n
(iv) where possible, the envisaged period for which my personal data will be stored, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;\n
(v) where personal data is not collected from me, any available data as to their source;\n
(vi) the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, pursuant to Article 22(1) and (4) GDPR, and, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and the envisaged consequences of such processing for me.\n
\n
My full name is %1$s and my corresponding email(s) is/are %2$s%3$s\n
\n
I am hereby executing my right to access that kind of information pursuant to Article 15(1) GDPR. It may be helpful for you to know that such a request should be responded to without undue delay and at the latest within one month (Rec. 59 GDPR).\n
\n
Thank you for your cooperation.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s
    </string>
    <string name="subject_learn_about_reminder">REMINDER: General Data Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Date sent
    -->
    <string name="body_learn_about_reminder">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I am writing further to my mail from %2$s in which I requested to confirm if you are processing any personal data concerning me on the basis of Article 15(1) GDPR, since I have not received any response from you.\n
\n
As the statutory time limit for a response has now expired, I would appreciate an immediate answer from you. If I do not receive an answer from you within the next 14 days, I will consider to lodge a complaint pursuant to Article 15(1) lit f GDPR.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>


    <!-- ACCESS -->
    <string name="subject_access">Data Access Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Primary email address
        3 - Optional email address
    -->
    <string name="body_access">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I am hereby requesting an electronic copy of all personal data concerning me undergoing processing by your organization pursuant to Article 15(1) and (3) GDPR.\n
\n
My full name is %1$s and my corresponding email(s) is/are %2$s, %3$s, etc.\n
\n
It may be helpful for you to know that a request for a data copy pursuant to Article 15(1) and (3) GDPR should be responded to without undue delay and at the latest within one month (Rec. 59 GDPR).\n
\n
Thank you for your cooperation.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>
    <string name="subject_access_reminder">REMINDER: Data Access Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Date sent
    -->
    <string name="body_access_reminder">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I am writing further to my mail from %2$s in which I requested a copy of my personal data undergoing processing by your organization on the basis of Article 15(1) and (3) GDPR, since I have not received any response from you.\n
\n
As the statutory time limit for a response has now expired, I would appreciate an immediate answer from you. If I do not receive an answer from you within the next 14 days, I will consider to lodge a complaint pursuant to Article 15(1) lit (f) GDPR.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>


    <!-- TRANSFER -->
    <string name="subject_transfer">Data Transfer Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Primary email address
        3 - Optional email address
        4 - Organization receiver
    -->
    <string name="body_transfer">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I would like to ask you to transfer any data concerning me to %4$s and am hereby executing of my right of portability pursuant to Article 20 GDPR.\n
\n
My full name is %1$s and my corresponding email(s) is/are %2$s, %3$s, etc.\n
\n
It may be helpful for you to know that a request for a data transfer pursuant to Article 20 GDPR should be responded to without undue delay and at the latest within one month (Rec. 59 GDPR).\n
\n
Thank you for your cooperation.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>
    <string name="subject_transfer_reminder">REMINDER: Data Transfer Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Date sent
        3 - Organization receiver
    -->
    <string name="body_transfer_reminder">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I am writing further to my mail from %2$s in which I requested a transfer of my personal data by your organization to %3$s on the basis of Article 20 GDPR, since I have not received any response from you.\n
\n
As the statutory time limit for a response has now expired, I would appreciate an immediate answer from you. If I do not receive an answer from you within the next 14 days, I will consider to lodge a complaint pursuant to Article 15(1) lit (f) GDPR.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>


    <!-- DELETE -->
    <string name="subject_delete">Erasure of Personal Data Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
    -->
    <string name="body_delete">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I would like to ask you to erase all personal data concerning me obtained by you without undue delay. Please confirm the erasure once executed. Furthermore, I would like you to confirm that if applicable, you have taken necessary steps pursuant to Article 17(2) GDPR.\n
\n
It may be helpful for you to know that a request for erasure of personal data pursuant to Article 17 GDPR should be responded to without undue delay and at the latest within one month (Recital 59 GDPR).\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>

    <string name="subject_delete_reminder">REMINDER: Erasure of Personal Data Request</string>
    <!--formatting
        1 - Full name
        2 - Date sent
    -->
    <string name="body_delete_reminder">Dear Sir or Madam,\n
\n
I am writing further to my mail from %2$s in which I requested to delete any personal data concerning me held by your organization on the basis of Article 17 GDPR, since I have not received any response from you.\n
\n
As the statutory time limit for a response has now expired, I would appreciate an immediate answer from you. If I do not receive an answer from you within the next 14 days, I will consider to lodge a complaint pursuant to Article 15(1) lit (f) GDPR.\n
\n
\n
Yours sincerely,\n
%1$s</string>

</resources>